infosecisland.com 2016-05-08

# Infosec Island

WireHead Security LLC operates the Infosec Island community and Infosec Island services. The Infosec Island community allows you to connect, communicate and collaborate with your friends and associates ("Connections") across the Internet while enjoying privacy and security usually found only on a private network. Connections are people you choose to connect with and who agree to connect with you.

Your privacy is very important to us. To help you understand how your privacy is protected we provide an explanation of various parts of the system below: By using Infosec Island, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in the Privacy Policy.  
Users have the option to edit their privacy settings. 

#### Information gathered by this site

For visitors to our website and registered users, we log standard technical information, such as your IP address. If you choose to register with us, Infosec Island requires you to provide your name, email address, and each subscriber has a user ID and password that they choose. To maintain privacy it is important not to share your password with anyone. Selecting a longer password with a mix of letters, numbers and symbols makes it more difficult for others to guess your password. It is also helpful to change passwords on a regular basis. In addition, Infosec Island may optionally ask you to provide your physical address and other demographic information, such as interests or occupation, and website address (URL). We may collect other personal information when you provide feedback or comments, or communicate with others through our systems.

Infosec Island uses cookies to administer its website and provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. For example, we may use cookies to count the number of unique computers accessing our website. This site also employs the use of JavaScript (in the form of certain AJAX calls) to make the site experience richer. You can set your browser to refuse cookies and JavaScript if you wish, but you will not be able to login.

#### Profile information

Your user profile contains information about you that you may want to share with others. The list of privacy setting for your profile includes options to provide information only to connections rather than all members. Other options allow you to specify how much and how broadly your profile information should be cached and viewable throughout the Infosec Island network or via the web.

Protecting the privacy of your profile is your responsibility: We caution you not to share sensitive information (such as social security numbers, credit card numbers, or driver's license numbers) with other users whom you do not know or place such information in your profile. 

We may use profile information for the purposes of providing our services to you, such as to analyze our demographics, or to better personalize our various offerings for users.

Additionally, any information you choose to display on the Infosec Island web site, including your profile, will be viewable by other members. Certain non-identifying information, including your "avatar" and "nickname" may be viewable by non-members. 

#### Groups

Groups are associations of people and content that can be shared and discussed within the network. In many cases the groups we choose to connect with help define our personality -- hobbies, favorite artists, current events we are passionate about, and organizations we belong to. The creator of a group may choose to make it open to everyone within the Infosec Island network or to restrict membership to a specific group of people they choose, or to allow potential members to apply.

#### Messages

When you communicate with a friend in a message we endeavor to ensure that the only people who receive or can read the message are those to whom you have intended to send it. 

#### Search

All search results in Infosec Island are personally generated for you based not only on what is popular, but also on what interests you based on your profile, groups you connect to, and what your connections connect to. Advertising results are also designed to be most relevant to you and be separated from your search results. Search results may link to other locations within the Infosec Island network or websites on the Internet. Data about searches and search results may be maintained by Infosec Island to help in continually improving the service.

#### Inviting others and sending notes

If you invite another person to join Infosec Island, we will ask for that person's name and online contact information. We use this information to contact and inform that person that he or she has been invited to join our network or to see something on our network. We will send reminders only with your express consent.

Invitations and comments are sent via email. These may be monitored for abuse.

#### Infosec Island's use of information

The information we collect about you in the course of our relationship is used to provide our software and services to you. For example, even as we endeavor to protect your identity, we may use your demographic information to create a database of user profiles, select advertisements based on your information and for marketing analysis. In addition, we look at technical information to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Infosec Island website, to enhance our products and to provide our service to you.

We may share personally identifiable information about our users with third parties, including: (1) with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (2) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (3) where required by law; or (4) at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights or property of Infosec Island or any third party.

In the event of a change of ownership or a direct merger with or acquisition by another entity, your information may be transferred to the acquiring entity. You have the option to request the removal of your account specific information at any time.

#### Third parties

Infosec Island may provide links to third party websites or allow other companies, called third-party ad servers, to display advertisements to users. Ad server companies can write and read their own cookies on your computer, just as if you had requested a web page from their website. Infosec Island is not responsible for, and does not have any control over, the privacy practices or the content of such third parties. We encourage users to read the privacy policies of any website visited.

#### Updating or removing user information

You may choose to correct or update the information you have submitted to us by editing your profile or account information. If you request to have your information removed, Infosec Island will remove it from its active database, though it may continue to persist on back-up media.

#### Changes to our policies

Infosec Island's Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make any substantive changes to our policies, we will notify registered users by posting bulletins on the Infosec Island service, by email at the address provided by you, or by posting notice of changes at http://www.infosecisland.com/privacy.html. Your use of the website or the Infosec Island Software after the changes constitutes your agreement with regard to information collected from you in the past and in the future.

#### Information storage and security

Infosec Island's computers store user account information, and may cache user profile information for backup and synchronization purposes. Infosec Island also maintains peer servers that can provide access to cached information when peers that would otherwise provide it are logged off of the network. Infosec Island employs industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Infosec Island allows folders to be shared privately with members of the Infosec Island network. Only friends who have been authorized to share a particular folder can see that the folder exists at all, see what objects are inside or access those objects. The objects in the folder remain on your system and are not cached or indexed in any way by the network. The contents of a group are cached within the network. When photos are shared with friends, they are uploaded to the Infosec Island server, and friends may be able to cache them. 

The Infosec Island software is designed so that the content you generate within the network (groups, blogs, forums, photo galleries, file collections, etc.) will have an associated privacy setting. If the information being created has its own privacy control (i.e. when creating a blog), it is the users responsibility to select the desired privacy setting upon creation. Other items may inherit an existing privacy setting. It is the user's responsibility to understand the associated privacy setting before creating content to ensure the handling of their information meets their expectations.

Please note that information stored or cached on other users' computers is subject to those users security practices, which are beyond Infosec Island's control. Although we make good faith efforts to store information collected or stored by Infosec Island in a secure manner, we cannot guarantee complete security. Information held by Infosec Island will be maintained for a length of time appropriate to our business needs.

Contacting us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of Infosec Island, or your experience with Infosec Island.com, please contact us at: [support@infosecisland.com](mailto://support@infosecisland.com).
